# **Kyleigh McKim**

Future nurse dedicated to study and practice

(936) 522-7761

kyleigh mckim1@baylor.edu
83 Lenox Hill Drive
The Woodlands TX, 77382
LinkedIn | Website

## **Profile**

A dedicated and outgoing student who strives to put her best foot forward at Baylor University while working toward becoming a Registered Nurse with a Minor in Film and Digital Media. Worked with both people and animals, gaining experience and knowledge along the way in the art of nursing. Well-rounded, with endeavors in both science and the arts.

# **Education**

# Baylor University August 2020 - Present

- Bachelor of Science in Nursing (BSN)
- GPA: 3.25 with 66 total hours
- Courses: Biology 2401 (Anatomy and Physiology), Nutrition 2351, Psychology 3341, and Chemistry 1300
- Member of the Baylor Future Nurses Association c
- Member of AMWA- Social Committee Member
- 3-week surgical skills course in phlebotomy, intubation, and IV insertion
- Expected Graduation: May 2024

## The Woodlands High School August 2016 - June 2020

- GPA: 3.90
- Courses in Biology and Anatomy
- Aid to the school nurses responsible for student care
- Graduating Member of NSHSS
- Competitor in SkillsUSA Audio/Film Sector and UIL Choir

# **Work Experience & Activities**

#### Behavioral Health Tech/Admissions June 2021 - present

Description: Admitting and assisting in patient care.

#### Farm Assistant, Morrison Farm June 2017 - June 2018

**Description**: Working out and examining horses for minor injuries, grooming horses before and after being ridden, tacking up horses for training rides, bathing horses, cleaning up the stable after other riders completed their lessons.

#### **Extracurricular Activities**

- 1 year of active FNA member
- Member of AMWA
- 12 Years of Competitive Equestrian Show Hunter/Jumping at Woodlands Farms and Manning Estate Stables
- 5 years of competitive UIL Choir

## **Skills**

- Fluent in Microsoft Office
- Experienced in the Adobe creative suite, including Photoshop and premiere
- Familiar with 3DS Max, Mudbox, and Blender
- Versed in Audio/Video Production and Photography
- Punctual, excellent communication skills, creative mindset, hardworking, and a positive attitude

# **Distinctions**

- Member, NSHSS
- Academic Letters
- Awarded by school's Nurse
- Allstate UIL Ensemble 1st Division and Sweepstakes
- 6th place overall in United States Hunter Jumper
- Association Zone 7's Pony Hunter Division - Pony Finals Qualifier
- Numerous ribbons USHJA Children's Hunter Class

# **Projects**

- High School Representative at CISD Teacher Convention
- High School Broadcast News Anchor
- Various Film and Photography projects with my classmates